

Kevin Nathanael Taufiek

- +6285155218871
- ★ kevin.taufiek@gmail.com
- https://kevinnathanaeltaufiek.github.io/
- Depok, Indonesia

SUMMARY

Currently a second-year computer science student at Bina Nusantara University, Software Engineering Stream program. Joined Binus Student Learning Community Organization (BSLC) as an IT Support activist and mentor. Understand the basics of computer science such as problem-solving, programming algorithms, and so on as well as soft skills such as leadership, communication, and collaboration. Became "Beasiswa Juara" scholarship awardee and became a scholarship mentor for 2 periods. Have an interest in Web Development (Front End and Back End) and Mobile Development. Have strong desire to become a developer.

EXPERIENCE

11/2020 - Present

IT Support

Binus Student Learning Community

- Ensure the content on the organization's website is appropriate
- · Manage data and content on website pages
- Responsible for data and content in the organization

10/2020 - 07/2021

Scholarship Mentor

Bina Nusantara University

- Managed study time and mentoring in study groups
- Assist & mentored mentees to achieve better grades
- · Motivate mentees to keep develop their skill

07/2019 - 08/2020

Education Counselor

Bina Nusantara University

- · Participated in campus tour events
- · Help students to find college majors that are suitable for them
- Promote scholarship program

EDUCATION

2023

Computer Science

Bina Nusantara University

Bachelor

- Became "Beasiswa Juara" scholarship awardee
- Became a scholarship mentor for 2 periods
- · Got a perfect GPS in the fourth semester

CERTIFICATES

07/2021 - Present Coding Studio Laravel Course

06/2021 - Present SoloLearn PHP Course

07/2020 - Present HackerRank Problem Solving Certificate

SKILLS

Java	Advanced	CSS	Intermediate
С	Advanced	Bootstrap	Intermediate
PHP	Intermediate	UI Design	Intermediate
C#	Intermediate	UX Design	Beginner
JavaScript	Beginner	Database Design	Intermediate
Object Oriented Programming / OOP	Advanced	SQL	Advanced
		MySQL	Intermediate
Data Structures	Intermediate	SQL Server	Advanced
Laravel	Intermediate	SQLite	Intermediate
ASP.NET	Intermediate	Android Studio	Intermediate
HTML	Advanced	API	Intermediate

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Intermediate